burgling_1
breaking into a house_2
burgling_3
cleaning the window_4
burgling_5
breaking into a house_6
burgling_7
breaking into a house_8
burgling_9
breaking into a house_10
trying to get into the house_11
he is trying to get into the house_12
he is trying to open the door_13
burgling_14
burglar_15
burgling_16
he is trying to get into the house_17
burgling_18
he is trying to open the door_19
breaking into a house_20
trying to get into the house_21
breaking into a house_22
trying to get into the house_23
breaking into a house_24
burgling_25
he is trying to open the door_26
breaking into a house_27
burgling_28
trying to break into the house_29
they are trying to open the door_30
they are trying to open the window_31
breaking into a house_32
they are trying to break into the house_33
breaking into a house_34
they are trying to break into the house_35
breaking into a house_36
burgling_37
breaking into a house_38
burgling
breaking into a house_39
trying to get into the house_40
burgling
breaking into a house_41
breaking into a house
breaking into a house_42
burgling
breaking into a house_43
trying to get into the house_44
breaking into a house
breaking into a house_45
burgling
trying to get into the house_46
breaking into a house
breaking into a house_47
he is cleaning the window
he is cleaning the window_48
burgling
burgling_49
burgling_50
he is trying to get into the house_51
trying to get into the house
burgling_52
he is trying to open the door
breaking into a house_53
breaking into a house
breaking into a house_54
cleaning the window_55
he is cleaning the window
vacuuming_56
vacuuming
he is trying to open the door_57
cleaning the window
cleaning the window_58
cleaning the window_59
the person is using a hose to clean the outside of the house_60
cleaning the window_61
breaking into a house_62